https://greendayonline.com/terms-of-use/#

Terms of UseGet Started Now Get Started Now! -- Requested Amount --$100.00$200.00$300.00$400.00$500.00$600.00$700.00$800.00$900.00$1000.00+
By clicking on "Get Started!", I agree to the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and ESIGN Consent
WEBSITE TERMS OF USE AGREEMENTWelcome to Greendayonline (referred to as “Company”, “we,” “us,” or “our”). Before you begin to use the Greendayonline website (“Company Website”), please take a moment to review this Terms of Use Agreement (“Agreement”). The Agreement describes the terms and conditions applicable to your use of the Company Website and the products and services provided through or in connection with the Company Website (collectively, “Service”).You must read and agree with all of the terms and conditions contained in this Agreement and the Company Website Privacy Policy then in effect (“Privacy Policy”), which is incorporated by reference, before you use our loan matching services. By accessing the Company Website, you agree to abide by the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, you may not use our Company Website.EligibilityUse of the services is limited to parties that lawfully can enter into and form contracts under applicable law. For example, minors are not allowed to use the service.PrivacyCompany respects your privacy. Use of our Site is also subject to the Terms and Conditions of our Privacy Policy. See Greendayonline’s privacy policy for additional information regarding your privacy on this website.If you have questions about these Terms of Use of the Privacy Policy please email info@Greendayonline.comLinks and ContentCompany is not responsible for, and cannot guarantee the performance of, any products and services provided by any advertisers or others to whose sites we link. A link to another website does not constitute an endorsement of that site (nor of any product, service or other material offered on that site) by Company or its licensors.While we try to ensure that any information we post to this website is both timely and accurate, errors may appear from time to time, since the Company Website is not updated daily. Therefore certain information may not be the most current information available. While we may post up to date information and reports, we may also continue to provide access to the original information and reports, as in an archive of news stories, for example, and we may not go back and change the original report to reflect new information. If you’re looking for the most recent information on a given subject be sure you’re not looking at an out of date report. Before you act on information you’ve found on our website, you should independently confirm any facts that are important to your decision.Although we make this website freely accessible, the materials available through this website are the property of Company or its licensors, and are protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. Except for the limited licenses expressly granted to you in this agreement, Company and its licensors expressly reserve all other rights and licenses. You are free to display and print for your personal, non-commercial use information you receive through this website, but you may not otherwise reproduce or modify any of the materials without the prior written consent of their owner. You may not distribute copies of materials found on this website in any form, without our prior written consent. Of course, you are free to encourage others to access the information themselves on this website and to tell them how to find it by linking to this site. Requests for permission to reproduce or distribute materials found on this website should be sent to info@Greendayonline.comWe welcome links to the homepage of our website. You are free to establish a hypertext link to the any part of this site so long as the link does not state or imply any affiliation with Company. We do not permit framing or inline linking to our website or any portion of it.TrademarksCompany and its trademarks and service marks, logos and product and service names and phrases, which Company no claims or may claim in the future, are trademarks of Company (the “Company marks”). You agree not to display or use the Company marks in any manner, without Company’s prior written permission.ViolationsYou should report any violations of the Agreement to info@Greendayonline.com.Submissions and PostingsYou are solely responsible for any information that you submit or post on this website. By using this website you agree not to submit, post or transmit any defamatory, abusive, obscene, threatening or illegal material, or any other material that infringes on the ability of others to enjoy this website or that infringes on the rights of others. We retain the right to deny access to anyone who we believe has violated these terms or any other term of this agreement.We reserve the right (but assume no obligation) to monitor, delete, move, or edit any submissions or postings that come to our attention that we consider unacceptable or inappropriate, whether for legal or other reasons. We will comply with all requirements of the law regarding disclosure of any submissions or postings on this website to others, including to law enforcement agencies and parties making civil legal requests. We will also comply with any other requirements of the law regarding disclosure of other aspects of your use of this website.TerminationCompany reserves the right at any time to terminate your use of this website if you fail to comply in full with any term of this agreement, or any other terms, agreements, or policies that apply to this website and the use of it.IndemnificationYou agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Company (including its parents, subsidiaries, and affiliates and all of their respective officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, suppliers and any third-party information providers) against all claims, losses, expenses, damages and costs (including reasonable attorney fees) resulting from any breach of this agreement or unauthorized use of this website. Your indemnification obligation shall survive the termination of this agreement. At our expense and election, we reserve the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you and you agree to cooperate with Company in connection with our defense.Disclaimer of Warranties and LiabilityYOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. BECAUSE OF THE NUMBER OF POSSIBLE SOURCES OF INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THE WEBSITE, AND THE INHERENT HAZARDS AND UNCERTAINTIES OF ELECTRONIC DISTRIBUTION, THERE MAY BE INTERRUPTIONS, DELAYS, OMISSIONS, INACCURACIES, OR OTHER PROBLEMS WITH SUCH INFORMATION. IF YOU RELY ON THIS WEBSITE OR ANY MATERIAL AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM ANY MATERIAL AND/OR DATA DOWNLOADED FROM OR OTHERWISE PROVIDED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE.THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU “AS IS,” “WITH ALL FAULTS,” AND “AS AVAILABLE.” COMPANY AND ITS AGENTS AND LICENSORS CANNOT AND DO NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, NONINFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OF THE INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THE WEBSITE, NOR DO THEY GUARANTEE THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE ERROR-FREE, OR CONTINUOUSLY AVAILABLE, OR THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL COMPANY (INCLUDING ITS PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AND AFFILIATES) OR ITS AGENTS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF ANY USE OR MISUSE OF THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR SIMILAR DAMAGES, EVEN IF ADVISED BEFOREHAND OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OR CAUSE OF ACTION INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, AND OTHER TORT ACTIONS. BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN CATEGORIES OF DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE LIABILITY OF COMPANY AND ITS AGENTS AND LICENSORS IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW. YOU AGREE THAT THE LIABILITY OF COMPANY (INCLUDING ITS PARENTS, SUBSIDIARIES, AND AFFILIATES) AND ITS AGENTS AND LICENSORS, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF ANY KIND OF LEGAL CLAIM IN ANY WAY CONNECTED TO THE WEBSITE SHALL NOT EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO COMPANY FOR THE USE OF THE WEBSITE.Exclusions and LimitationsSome jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental or consequential damages. Accordingly, some of the above limitations may not apply to you. To the extent a court determines any provisions in this Agreement to be unenforceable; such a determination shall not affect the validity of the remaining terms of this Agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect.Arbitration ProvisionBy visiting and/or using the Company Website from within the United States, you agree that the laws of the State of Delaware, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern this Agreement and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Company or its affiliates.IN THE EVENT OF ANY CONTROVERSY, CLAIM OR DISPUTE BETWEEN THE PARTIES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THIS AGREEMENT OR THE BREACH, TERMINATION, ENFORCEMENT, INTERPRETATION OR VALIDITY THEREOF, INCLUDING THE TERMINATION OF THE SCOPE OR APPLICABILITY OF THIS AGREEMENT TO ARBITRATE, SHALL BE DETERMINED BY ARBITRATION IN DELAWARE OR IN THE COUNTY IN WHICH THE CONSUMER RESIDES, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF THE STATE OF DELAWARE FOR AGREEMENTS TO BE MADE IN AND TO BE PERFORMED IN DELAWARE. THE PARTIES AGREE, THE ARBITRATION SHALL BE ADMINISTERED BY THE AMERICAN ARBITRATION ASSOCIATION (“AAA”) PURSUANT TO ITS RULES AND PROCEDURES AND AN ARBITRATOR SHALL BE SELECTED BY THE AAA. THE ARBITRATOR SHALL BE NEUTRAL AND INDEPENDENT AND SHALL COMPLY WITH THE AAA CODE OF ETHICS. THE AWARD RENDERED BY THE ARBITRATOR SHALL BE FINAL AND SHALL NOT BE SUBJECT TO VACATION OR MODIFICATION. JUDGMENT ON THE AWARD MADE BY THE ARBITRATOR MAY BE ENTERED IN ANY COURT HAVING JURISDICTION OVER THE PARTIES. IF EITHER PARTY FAILS TO COMPLY WITH THE ARBITRATOR’S AWARD, THE INJURED PARTY MAY PETITION THE CIRCUIT COURT FOR ENFORCEMENT. THE PARTIES AGREE THAT EITHER PARTY MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER ONLY IN HIS/HER OR ITS INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. FURTHER, THE PARTIES AGREE THAT THE ARBITRATOR MAY NOT CONSOLIDATE PROCEEDINGS OF MORE THAN ONE PERSON’S CLAIMS, AND MAY NOT OTHERWISE PRESIDE OVER ANY FORM OF REPRESENTATIVE OR CLASS PROCEEDING. THE PARTIES SHALL SHARE THE COST OF ARBITRATION, INCLUDING ATTORNEYS FEES, EQUALLY. IF THE CONSUMERS SHARE OF THE COST IS GREATER THAN $1,000.00 (ONE-THOUSAND DOLLARS), THE COMPANY WILL PAY THE CONSUMERS SHARE OF COSTS IN EXCESS OF THAT AMOUNT.IN THE EVENT A PARTY FAILS TO PROCEED WITH ARBITRATION, UNSUCCESSFULLY CHALLENGES THE ARBITRATOR’S AWARD, OR FAILS TO COMPLY WITH THE ARBITRATOR’S AWARD, THE OTHER PARTY IS ENTITLED TO COSTS OF SUIT, INCLUDING A REASONABLE ATTORNEY’S FEE FOR HAVING TO COMPEL ARBITRATION OR DEFEND OR ENFORCE THE AWARD.Additional Dispute ResolutionAny other Disputes will be Resolved as Follows:If a dispute arises under this agreement, we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed upon mediator. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.By using this website, you agree to abide by this Terms of Use Agreement.Notices and EmailYou agree that Company may submit any notices to you via either e-mail or regular mail. The service may also provide notices by displaying notices or links to notices to you generally on the service, which notice you also agree Company may submit to you via e-mail or regular mail.We may periodically change the Terms of Use and the Site without notice, and you are responsible for checking these Terms of Use periodically for revisions. All amended Terms of Use become effective upon our posting to the Site, and any use of the site after such revisions have been posted signifies your consent to the changes.Questions and CommentsWe invite you to send in your questions or comments about this website, or to bring to our attention any material you believe to be inaccurate. You may provide general feedback by emailing us at info@Greendayonline.com.
